PAIGE BOYD

PRODUCT DESIGNER

www.paigeboyd.co.uk

Profile

I am a self motivated, enthusiastic Digital Product Designer and recent graduate of BDes (Hons) Interaction Design.

I design intuitive digital products with a focus on creating a meaningful user experience. I am fascinated with technology and the potential it has to enhance our lives.

I enjoy getting involved in every stage of the Product Design process, and always strive to learn new skills to better myself as a designer.



Experience

Freelance Product Designer Paige Boyd Designs Ltd August 2017 - Present

Worked with a variety of clients across multiple industries to design websites, apps and platforms that align business needs with needs of customers. Worked as part of a team, as the lead designer and also as the only designer in the team. Experience in collaborating with developers and directly with clients to create their perfect solution.

Clients include:

Danske Bank, Relative Ltd, Funds-Axis, Assistant.ly, Finmondo.

Multimedia Content Designer Intern Ulster University

September 2016 - June 2017

Worked within the University's CMS to design and implement the webpages for Belfast School of Art to align with the University's new brand.

Designed promotional materials using Adobe Illustrator and InDesign for School events.



Interests

UI/UX Accessibility

Vector Illustration Design for Social Good Responsive Design Emerging Technologies

Education

BDes (Hons) Interaction Design Ulster University, Belfast School of Art September 2014 - July 2018

Award: First Class Honours and Diploma in Professional Practice with Commendation. Deans List in Years 1 & 2.

Modules: Interaction Design, Designing with Content, UX & UI, Narrative & Storytelling, Dissertation Writing, Major Project Prototyping.



Achievements

Deloitte Digital Experience Award June 2018

The Deloitte Digital Experience Award recognises outstanding skill and creative thinking in Interaction Design. Awarded for: Signar (degree major project).

EDGE Award June 2018

Supported by Ulster University and PwC to recognise extra-curricular activities that aid student employability.



Design Toolkit

Illustrator Pen & Paper
Adobe XD Sketch
InDesign Webflow
Photoshop Figma
After Effects HTML & CSS

Proto.io Axure



Contact

design@paigeboyd.co.uk 07710884634

🏏 @ppppaige_

References available on request.